<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Omnigram on Omnigram App Docs</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/</link><description>Recent content in Omnigram on Omnigram App Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Mermaid</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/api/example/mermaid/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/api/example/mermaid/</guid><description>Mermaid is library that helps you generate diagrams, flowcharts, and piecharts from text in a similar manner as markdown.
With compose theme, you can use mermaid using a custom shortcode as follows:
Sequence Diagrams Syntax
1{{&amp;lt; mermaid &amp;gt;}} 2sequenceDiagram 3 participant Alice 4 participant Bob 5 Alice-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Hello John, how are you? 6 loop Healthcheck 7 John-&amp;gt;&amp;gt;John: Fight against hypochondria 8 end 9 Note right of John: Rational thoughts&amp;lt;br/&amp;gt;prevail... 10 John--&amp;gt;&amp;gt;Alice: Great!</description></item><item><title>Best Practice For Install</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/install/best_practice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/install/best_practice/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/install/requirements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/install/requirements/</guid><description>Software Dependencies Docker
Hardware Requirements System: Unix-like systems (Ubuntu, Debian, CentOS, MacOS, etc.) [preferred], Windows; Memory: Minimum 1GB, recommended 4GB or more CPU: Minimum 2 cores, recommended 4 cores or more GPU: If using the localized AI audiobook feature and AI-assisted reading, vRAM of 8GB or more is required</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/overview/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/overview/getting-started/</guid><description>Dependencies Please refer to environment requirements for details.
Docker Startup By default, after docker starts up it will create a default admin account admin with the default password 123456.
The default password is 123456. You can change it after logging in later, or by setting the OMNI_PASSWORD environment variable. my_local_docs_path should be modified to your actual directory path that stores Epubs and PDFs. After logging in, you can configure scanning strategies to build file indices.</description></item><item><title>Support this project</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/overview/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/docs/overview/support/</guid><description>I have a firm commitment to this project. I will continue to update the documentation, add new features, and fix bugs. However, this is an enormous task that I cannot accomplish alone. Therefore, I need your help to give me extra motivation to persist.
If you feel this is a valuable project and can envision yourself using this application long-term, please consider supporting the project through one of the options below.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/privacy_policy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/privacy_policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy
Sven Liu built the Omnigram app as an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by Sven Liu at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/terms_conditions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://omnigram.nexptr.com/en/terms_conditions/</guid><description>Terms &amp;amp; Conditions
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions.</description></item></channel></rss>